[
    {
        "front": "とい",
        "back": "問い \nenquiry",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "もんだい",
        "back": "問題 \nproblem, question",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "しつもん",
        "back": "質問 \nquestion",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "もんだい",
        "back": "問題 \nproblem, question",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "わだい",
        "back": "話題 \ntopic",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅくだい",
        "back": "宿題 \nhomework",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいめい",
        "back": "題名 \ntitle",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "ためす",
        "back": "試す \nto test, to try",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "しけん",
        "back": "試験 \nexam",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "しあい",
        "back": "試合 \nmatch",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "にゅうし",
        "back": "入試 \nentrance exam",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "しけん",
        "back": "試験 \nexam",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "けいけん",
        "back": "経験 \nexperience",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "じっけん",
        "back": "実験 \nexperiment",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "じっけん（する）",
        "back": "実験 （する） \nto give exam",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "しつ",
        "back": "質 \nquality",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "しつもん",
        "back": "質問 \nquestion",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひんしつ",
        "back": "品質 \nproduct quality",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "あう",
        "back": "合う \nto match",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "ばあい",
        "back": "場合 \nin case of",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "しあい",
        "back": "試合 \nmatch, game",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "つごう",
        "back": "都合 \nconvenience, schedule",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "こたえ",
        "back": "答え \nanswer",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいとう",
        "back": "回答 \nanswer, reply",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "こたえる",
        "back": "答える \nto answer",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "もちいる",
        "back": "用いる \nto use",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "しよう",
        "back": "使用 \nuse",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "こどもよう",
        "back": "子ども用 \nfor children use",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "しようきんし",
        "back": "使用禁止 \ndo not use",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "利用する",
        "back": "利用する \nutilization, to use a service",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "かみ",
        "back": "紙 \npaper",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "もんだいようし",
        "back": "問題用紙 \nquestion paper",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいとうようし",
        "back": "解答用紙 \nanswer sheet",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "てがみ",
        "back": "手紙 \nletter",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "いみ",
        "back": "意味 \nmeaning",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうい",
        "back": "注意 \ncaution, warning",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "ようい（する）",
        "back": "用意（する） \nto prepare",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    },
    {
        "front": "いけん",
        "back": "意見 \nopinion",
        "chapter": "N4 K19"
    }
]